[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐声]
ADDY OSMANI: So welcome to Totally Tooling Tips.
欢迎使用完全工具提示
This is an episode on DevTools, where
这是关于开发工具的一集，
we're going to talk about our newer, progressive Web App
我们将讨论渐进式Web App工具的最新应用
MATT GAUNT: Yeah.
是的
So the reason we have to do this is we record an entire video
我们这样做的原因是因为我们记录了整集
episode and then everything changed.
然后一切都变了。
ADDY OSMANI: It's Tuesday, so DevTools has changed.
现在是星期二，因此开发工具已更改。
Right.
没错
So the resources panel has now been
资源视图面板已更改
replaced by the shiny, new application panel.
替换为“全新应用”视图。
So I'm currently on Progressive Web App.
我现在正在开发渐进式Web App
This is smaller pictures.
这些是较小的图像
And some of the newer stuff that we let you preview
还有一些我们可以预览的新功能
include your Web App Manifest.
包括您的网络应用程序声明。
MATT GAUNT: Yeah.
是的
So basically, Web App Manifest is kind of,
基本上，网络应用程序清单是一种
if you've ever built Web Apps or you've
如果网络应用程序已构建或
had to do icons for different devices and browsers,
如果您必须为不同的设备和浏览器设置图标，
and you had to put in lots of link tags,
我不得不放很多链接标签，
Manifest is a JSON file where you
应用程序清单是一个JSON文件，您可以在其中
can put all of that stuff in one separate resource.
将所有这些内容放在单独的资源中。
And the browser will only go and grab it when it needs it.
-浏览器仅在需要时才捕获它。
ADDY OSMANI: Yep.
因此，我们总结了您的名字和您的简称的所有内容，
through the different theme colors and background colors
浏览您使用的颜色和主题。
We show you your orientation chosen in your manifest file,
并在清单中显示您选择的方向，
and then just preview all the different icon sizes
然后预览所有不同的图标大小
you might have set up.
您创建的。
So I've got all of them because I'm crazy.
我拥有这一切是因为我疯了。
MATT GAUNT: You are crazy.
是的，你是。
ADDY OSMANI: I am crazy.
我是
It also lets you emulate as the home screen,
它还使您可以将其模拟为主屏幕，
if you click on this little link here.
如果您单击此处的小链接。
That's just like the experience where it'll show you, OK, well
就像您看到的体验，好，很好
what do you wanna name this thing?
您想给这件事起什么名字？
MATT GAUNT: So the reason this is
这很重要，因为每当您按添加到主屏幕时
of the criteria that Chrome looks for to basically decide
Chrome寻求所有标准作为决策依据
whether it's going to show the user the banner or not.
是否向用户展示薰衣草。
So it'll be things like, does the Web App
事情会变得像，您有一个应用程序
have a Service Worker?
网络服务工作者？他有一个简短的名字吗？
Does it have a theme color?
它有外观颜色吗？
And if any of those criteria aren't
如果不满足这些条件之一
met, it will print out an error to the console,
会为控制台打印一个错误，
just saying, yeah, you need to have this.
它写在里面，是的，你必须有这个。
And because it's not there, I can't do Add to Home Screen.
由于不存在，因此无法添加到主屏幕。
ADDY OSMANI: Cool.
太好了
So the next thing we're going to take a look at
所以接下来我们要看的是
is the Service Worker panel.
服务人员显示面板。
So debugging Service Worker has been historically
历史上纠正了服务人员
really, really painful.
非常非常痛苦
And I think DevTools has nicely evolved over time
我认为开发工具随着时间的推移已经有了显着的发展
to make that experience a little bit sweeter.
为了使体验更好一点。
MATT GAUNT: Yeah.
是的
This is definitely the best version of it.
这些绝对是最好的副本。
It's just really hard, when you're starting out,
刚开始就很困难
to understand what is going on when you're doing
了解您的情况
this stuff for the first time.
这些东西是第一次。
But I think it's definitely the nicest version so far.
但是我认为这绝对是最好的版本。
ADDY OSMANI: So we're going to quickly walk through
因此，我们将在此处快速浏览所有选项。
So the first one is an offline check box.
因此，第一个命令是“离线”复选框。
And basically, if we go and we refresh,
基本上，如果我们进行更新，
you'll see that the app is working offline.
您会看到该应用程序可以离线运行
This just emulates offline in the same way
这只是以相同方式离线模拟
that the network throttling drop down will let you do.
从中可以控制网格宽度。
MATT GAUNT: Nice.
太好了
ADDY OSMANI: Fairly useful when you're testing offline support
扫描离线支持时非常有用
with Service Worker.
与服务人员。
The next option is Update on Reload,
下一个选项是重新加载时更新
which forces your Service Worker script to update on refresh.
这会迫使您的Service Worker脚本在更新时进行修改。
MATT GAUNT: So the reason this is
原因是
super handy is before this existed, what you'd have to do
非常有用的是，在此之前，您应该做的事情
is you'd make an edit to your Service Worker, you'd save it,
是为了对您保存的Service Worker进行调整，
you'd go back into your browser, you'd refresh.
您将需要返回到已更新的浏览器。
And once you've refreshed the page,
页面出现时，
it will still be using the old Service
旧的服务人员将继续使用
Worker because your new Service Worker will be grabbed
因为新的Service Worker将由浏览器采用，
and the new Service Worker can't take over the page
新的Service Worker无法控制页面
until the old one is gone.
直到老消失了。
So when you check update on reload, what it's doing
因此，当您选择重载更新时，它的作用是
is it will unregister the old Service Worker,
将会取消旧的服务人员注册，
register the new one, and once the new one's ready to go,
它记录新内容，并在新内容准备好时，
it'll refresh the page so then the page
该页面将出现
is using the new Service Worker.
该页面使用新的Service Worker。
So it's one checkbox, but there's
所以这是一个复选框-但是有
kind of a lot of stuff going on behind the scenes
许多事情在幕后发生
and it's super useful.
这是非常有用的。
ADDY OSMANI: Next up, we've got Bypass
接下来，我们有
for Network, which will bypass your Service Worker script
绕过网络，这将避免使用Service Worker脚本
and load resources from the network.
它从网络加载资源。
MATT GAUNT: The reason this is handy
之所以有用的原因
is when you're not working on a Service Worker
那是当您不在Service Worker上时
and you're working on other files,
并适用于其他文件，
you don't want anything to be pulled from the cache.
您不希望任何内容被拉出缓存。
You just want to be using the files that you've just changed.
您只想使用刚修改的文件。
ADDY OSMANI: Yep.
是的
Then we've got Show All.
然后，Lena全部显示。
And Show All will basically show you every single Service
它将向您显示所有注册的服务人员。
Because we've got an increasing number of sites and apps
因为我们拥有越来越多的网站和应用程序
using this, you might find this a little bit noisy.
使用它，您可能会发现这很烦人。
MATT GAUNT: I'd just say, you're very unlikely to ever want
我想说，您不太可能想要，
this, until something like foreign Service Workers
直到出现外部服务工作者的情况
ADDY OSMANI: We're just letting you know that it exists today.
我们只是让您知道它的存在。
Unless they change it tomorrow.
除非明天改变。
But it's here, today, at least.
但是至少在今天。
What else does this let you do?
你还能做什么？知道了
OK.
您可以编辑您的服务人员。
There's a Push option as well.
还有一个“推送”选项。
What does that do?
他在做什么？让我们澄清一下。
MATT GAUNT: I'm going to guess it's going to do something
我想他会做点什么
with push messages.
带有付款信息。
ADDY OSMANI: You're so bright, Matthew.
马修，你真聪明。没错
Right.
这是Matt前一段时间写的付款说明。
We're going to go and we're going
我们去，我们会
to enable push notifications.
通过启用推送通知。
Your demo worked this time.
我这次工作很成功。
MATT GAUNT: Yes!
是的
ADDY OSMANI: Right.
没错
So what we're going to do is, if we click Push,
如果我们按Push，我们将做什么
it's going to emulate a push event.
它将模拟付款事件。
And you'll see that we get a push notification.
您会看到我们正在收到推送通知。
MATT GAUNT: And this is kind of interesting
这很有趣
because this is the first time I've actually seen or tested
因为这是我第一次看到或测试
this myself in Canary.
这个我自己在金丝雀。
And they basically added a new feature
他们添加了新功能
where it's populating a little bit of data in there, which
他在那里限定一些数据的地方，
is kind of super interesting, slightly weird with the fact
这很有趣，事实有点奇怪
that you can't determine what the data is,
您无法确定哪些数据，
but it's awesome that it's there because it
但是它的存在真是太好了，因为
does mean that if you wanted to check what data would look
这意味着您是否要检查数据格式
like when it comes in your Service Worker,
当您来到服务人员时，
it's now something that's there.
现在已经存在了。
It's awesome.
-他很棒-好漂亮
And what happens if we click Send a Push via XHR?
如果单击“通过XHR发送推”，会发生什么情况？
Does anything happen?
有什么事吗
MATT GAUNT: It should do.
你必须
Doesn't actually-- oh, I didn't.
其实-我没有。
MATT GAUNT: Oh no, you did.
不，你有。
GCM just took a while to kick in.
GCM花了一些时间才能开始。
So there, because there's no data,
因为没有数据，
it's just like a super generic, thanks
非常一般，谢谢
for sending this message.
发送此消息。
ADDY OSMANI: Sweet.
太好了
You can also go and click on the little name.
您可以单击小名。
Oh, you got a minified Service Worker.
您有一个最小化的Service Worker。
MATT GAUNT: Yeah, man.
是的
ADDY OSMANI: What do you-- OK, let's
什么-好，走吧
go to someone who hasn't done that.
给一个没有的人。
And if we click on Source, you can go
如果我们点击来源，您可以
and you can check out the source to your Service Workers.
并选择服务人员的来源。
MATT GAUNT: He just doesn't care about user's data.
它只是不在乎用户数据。
So the reason this is actually super cool
这是如此奇妙的原因
is the fact that you can now add breakpoints
您可以添加断点的事实
to your Service Worker, like you would any normal JavaScript
对于您的Service Worker，就像任何普通的JavaScript文件一样。
So when that code gets executed in the Service Worker,
因此，当程序在Service Worker中运行时，
it will actually stop the Service Worker from running
服务人员实际上将关闭
and you can start debugging stuff like you normally
您可以从调试开始
would with DevTools.
通常使用开发工具。
Which is nice.
太好了
ADDY OSMANI: Sweet.
好漂亮
So you can see that we've got these activity
所以您可以看到我们有指标
indicators for the Status.
此案例的活动。
So green means that something is active and it's running.
绿色表示有效且已实施。
You can stop your Service Workers, we can go and do that.
您可以停止Service Worker，我们可以。
It'll say Activate and Stopped.
将激活并停止。
Or you can focus your client-- so we're currently focused.
或者，您可以关注您的客户-我们现在专注。
And also hit Details and it'll show you,
然后单击详细信息，您将看到，
in line, any of the exceptions or error messages
在主题内，没有异常或错误消息
you've been getting.
您正在接收。
MATT GAUNT: So the one thing that
那在那里
used to exist here that's been removed
在这里被删除
is you used to be able to have like an Inspect button
是你可以有一个检查按钮
that you would click and it would
你可以点击
open up an entirely different DevTools just
它将打开其他开发工具
for Service Worker.
仅适用于服务人员。
I still kind of like having the two DevTools, one for the page,
我仍然喜欢拥有两个开发工具，一个用于页面，
one for Service Worker, but I think
还有一个供服务人员使用
the DevTools team are trying to get everyone
我认为开发工具团队正在努力使每个人
to work just out of the one DevTools
他们只使用一种开发工具
and change different context.
并更改不同的上下文。
So in this case, all the Service Worker logs
因此，在这种情况下，所有Service Worker日志
will show up in the one console, and you select different frames
它会出现在控制台中，您可以在其中选择其他窗口
So it's kind of interesting.
所以这很有趣。
It's the only thing that I'm anxious about, I guess.
我认为这是唯一让我担心的事情。
But this is quite a nice way of at least servicing just
但这是解决错误的好方法。
ADDY OSMANI: Because I'm ADD, I'm just going to click clear
因为我患有注意力缺陷障碍，所以我将单击“删除”
and now all of our problems have gone.
现在您所有的问题都消失了。
MATT GAUNT: If only life was that simple.
如果生活就是这么简单。
Clear storage is basically the best thing ever.
清理存储是有史以来最好的事情。
If you're developing any non-trivial progressive Web App
如果要开发任何非平凡的渐进式Web应用程序
and you're trying to support offline with Service Workers,
而且您正在尝试与服务工作者脱机支持，
you're maybe using a storage mechanism
您可能正在使用存储机制
like IndexedDB, a local storage or session storage,
作为IndexedDB-并且是本地存储或会话存储
you've probably run into the situation where
您经常遇到一种情况
you need to manually go in and clear
您需要手动清洁
all of your different storage mechanisms out,
所有不同的存储机制
and then head to different panels
然后去不同的显示面板
to unregister Service Workers.
取消注册服务工作者。
And it's just-- it's this whole super tedious thing.
只是-这很累。
MATT GAUNT: Yeah.
是的
I've ended up writing helper scripts
最终我写了帮助脚本并开始
that I just drop into the console to delete everything.
只需将其放在控制台中即可删除所有内容。
Yeah.
到那个阶段，这很烦人。
ADDY OSMANI: So in an effort to make Matt Gaunt redundant,
因此，为了使Matt Gont变得毫无用处
there's now a clear site--
现在有一个清洁场所
MATT GAUNT: Well, that escalated quickly.
好吧，这很快就升级了。
ADDY OSMANI: There's now a Clear Site Data button.
现在有一个“清除站点数据”按钮。
I think the label for this might be changing.
我认为这样做的标记可能会改变。
The button is still there.
该按钮仍然存在。
Basically, what this does is it almost
基本上，这几乎是
resets the world for you, which is kind of really nice.
将世界重置为您，这真是太好了。
It does all the things it says above,
做上面写的所有事情，
like it will unregister your Service
例如，他们取消注册
Workers and your storage, and clear out your cache API
您的服务人员和您的存储空间，
MATT GAUNT: And yeah, this does seem like an obvious feature,
是的，这似乎是一个明显的优势，
but at the same time it hasn't existed for the longest time.
但是同时很久以前不存在了。
And when you start working with Service Workers,
当您开始使用Service Worker时，
you realize how quickly you just get into a mess
实现混乱的速度
and you just want to reset everything.
并且只想重置所有内容。
And the old solution for that was
对此的旧解决方案是
to just develop in Incognito Windows,
只是去隐藏的窗户，
so this is super welcome.
因此，这是非常受欢迎的。
ADDY OSMANI: This is so nice.
这绝对是太棒了。
We were talking about cache storage.
谈论临时记忆。
Because this was Resources Panel,
因为这是资源显示面板，
you can still go in and debug all of your different storage
您可以访问并更正所有不同的存储机制
That includes the cache API.
这包括API缓存。
So in the case of my app, I'm using sw-precache.
因此，就我而言，我使用sw-precache。
So I have all these entries.
所以我有所有这些输入。
For someone like Paul Lewis's voice memos app, we go in here
对于有人为Paul Lewis进行语音注释的应用程序，请进入此处
and you'll just see that there's an entry that's
你会发现那里有一个入口
got all the different files listed that he's
包含列出的所有不同文件
got cached in the cache API.
暂时将它们存储在API缓存中。
ADDY OSMANI: Shh.
闭嘴
It's all perfect.
一切都很完美。
It's all perfectly perfect.
一切都是完美的。
And you've also got other options in here, like frames.
您在这里还有其他选择，例如轮胎。
MATT GAUNT: Don't just say that like it is.
别那样说
No one knows what frames is.
没有人知道什么框架。
ADDY OSMANI: I don't know what this does anymore.
我不知道这会做什么。
It's basically a breakdown of different things.
这只是几件事的零碎。
MATT GAUNT: It's just like a list
它是可下载资产的列表。
ADDY OSMANI: Different assets.
不同的资产。
Let's assume that it does that.
假设他们这样做。
Maybe this gives us something to do another episode on.
也许这给我们做了另一件事。
MATT GAUNT: Next week on Totally Tooling Mini Tips.
下周将介绍Totally Tooling Mini Tips。
What is frames under Applications tab?
“应用程序”选项卡下的窗口是什么？
ADDY OSMANI: All right.
知道了
So I feel enlightened.
我感到受过教育。
That is the Application tab.
这是“应用程序”选项卡
Is there anything we're forgetting?
有我们忘记的东西吗？
ADDY OSMANI: I've got device art.
我有装置美术。
So Canary DevTools now let's you like preview device art
Canary开发工具现在可让您预览Device Art
for a few different devices.
对于几种不同的设备。
So we've got the Nexus 5x in there,
那里有Nexus 5x，
I think the six might also have device art?
我认为六个人可能拥有装置艺术？
It does not.
没有。我认为他拥有最新版本。
MATT GAUNT: So it's coming.
所以他来了。是的
But basically, device art is awesome.
但基本上，设备艺术很棒。
Just lets you see what it would maybe
你可以看到
look like on an actual device.
它看起来像一台真正的机器。
MATT GAUNT: And it adds in the navigation
它还添加了一个跳杆
bar at the top and other stuff, so it's nice.
在其他方面，这很棒。
and get your little navigation bar in.
并获得一点跳跃吧。
I have asked for us to take theme color into account.
我要求我们考虑外观颜色。
MATT GAUNT: Oh yeah.
是的
ADDY OSMANI: You could do that.
你可以做到这一点。
MATT GAUNT: That would be really nice.
这将非常酷。
And then it would-- yeah.
然后是-是的。
ADDY OSMANI: Assume that, by the time you've seen this,
假设直到看到此为止，
maybe we've convinced them and this is already out of date.
我们可能已经说服了他们，这对他不利。
MATT GAUNT: And if not, raise issues.
如果没有，请提起诉讼。
ADDY OSMANI: Raise issues.
提出一个问题。
MATT GAUNT: And maybe we can get it.
有可能赢。
ADDY OSMANI: All right.
知道了
So that is the Application tab.
这是“应用程序”选项卡。
Hopefully you'll find that a lot of the stuff
希望你发现很多东西
makes it a lot easier to develop and debug your progressive Web
它使开发和调试渐进式Web应用程序变得更加容易。
That's it from us.
就是这样
MATT GAUNT: Thanks for listening.
感谢您的收听。
ADDY OSMANI: Bye.
再见